[   {"question": "⼀", "answer": "one", "sound":"iti"},
    {"question": "⼁", "answer": "line", "sound":"si"},
    {"question": "⼂", "answer": "dot", "sound":"tenn"},
    {"question": "⼃", "answer": "slash | bend", "sound":"no"},
    {"question": "⼄ | ⺃", "answer": "second (position) ", "sound":"otsu"},
    {"question": "⼅", "answer": "hook", "sound":"ketsu"},
    {"question": "⼆", "answer": "two", "sound":"ni"},
    {"question": "⼇", "answer": "lid", "sound":""},
    {"question": "⼈ | ⺅| 𠆢", "answer": "person", "sound":""},
    {"question": "⼉", "answer": "legs (human)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "⼊", "answer": "enter", "sound":""},
    {"question": "⼋", "answer": "eight", "sound":""},
    {"question": "冂", "answer": "upside down box | enclose", "sound":""},
    {"question": "冖", "answer": "cover", "sound":""},
    {"question": "冫", "answer": "ice", "sound":""},
    {"question": "几", "answer": "table (small)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "凵", "answer": "open box", "sound":""},
    {"question": "刀", "answer": "knife", "sound":""},
    {"question": "力", "answer": "power", "sound":""},
    {"question": "勹", "answer": "wrap", "sound":""},
    {"question": "匕", "answer": "spoon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "匚", "answer": "box", "sound":""},
    {"question": "匸", "answer": "hide (conceal)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "十", "answer": "ten", "sound":""},
    {"question": "卜", "answer": "divination (oracle)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "卩", "answer": "seal | stamp", "sound":""},
    {"question": "厂", "answer": "cliff", "sound":""},
    {"question": "厶", "answer": "private", "sound":""},
    {"question": "又", "answer": "again | right hand", "sound":""},
    {"question": "口", "answer": "mouth", "sound":""},
    {"question": "囗", "answer": "enclosure | border", "sound":""},
    {"question": "土", "answer": "dirt", "sound":""},
    {"question": "士", "answer": "scholar", "sound":""},
    {"question": "夂", "answer": "go | follow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "夊", "answer": "go slowly", "sound":""},
    {"question": "夕", "answer": "evening", "sound":""},
    {"question": "大", "answer": "big", "sound":""},
    {"question": "女", "answer": "woman | female", "sound":""},
    {"question": "子", "answer": "child", "sound":""},
    {"question": "宀", "answer": "roof", "sound":""},
    {"question": "寸", "answer": "thumb", "sound":""},
    {"question": "小", "answer": "small", "sound":""},
    {"question": "尢", "answer": "lame (leg)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "尸", "answer": "corpse", "sound":""},
    {"question": "屮", "answer": "sprout", "sound":""},
    {"question": "山", "answer": "mountain", "sound":""},
    {"question": "巛", "answer": "river", "sound":""},
    {"question": "工", "answer": "work", "sound":""},
    {"question": "己", "answer": "oneself", "sound":""},
    {"question": "巾", "answer": "cloth | scarf", "sound":""},
    {"question": "干", "answer": "dried", "sound":""},
    {"question": "幺", "answer": "short", "sound":""},
    {"question": "广", "answer": "dotted cliff", "sound":""},
    {"question": "廴", "answer": "long stride", "sound":""},
    {"question": "廾", "answer": "two hands", "sound":""},
    {"question": "弋", "answer": "shoot | arrow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "弓", "answer": "bow (archery)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "彐", "answer": "snout (pig)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "彡", "answer": "bristle | beard", "sound":""},
    {"question": "彳", "answer": "step", "sound":""},
    {"question": "心", "answer": "heart", "sound":""},
    {"question": "戈", "answer": "halberd | spear", "sound":""},
    {"question": "戶", "answer": "door", "sound":""},
    {"question": "手", "answer": "hand", "sound":""},
    {"question": "支", "answer": "branch", "sound":""},
    {"question": "攴", "answer": "strike", "sound":""},
    {"question": "文", "answer": "script", "sound":""},
    {"question": "斗", "answer": "dipper", "sound":""},
    {"question": "斤", "answer": "axe", "sound":""},
    {"question": "方", "answer": "square", "sound":""},
    {"question": "无", "answer": "negative", "sound":""},
    {"question": "日", "answer": "day | sun", "sound":""},
    {"question": "曰", "answer": "say", "sound":""},
    {"question": "月", "answer": "moon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "木", "answer": "tree", "sound":""},
    {"question": "欠", "answer": "lack | yawn", "sound":""},
    {"question": "止", "answer": "stop", "sound":""},
    {"question": "歹", "answer": "death | decay", "sound":""},
    {"question": "殳", "answer": "weapon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "毋", "answer": "mother | do not", "sound":""},
    {"question": "比", "answer": "compare", "sound":""},
    {"question": "毛", "answer": "fur", "sound":""},
    {"question": "氏", "answer": "clan", "sound":"shi"},
    {"question": "气", "answer": "steam", "sound":""},
    {"question": "水", "answer": "water", "sound":""},
    {"question": "火", "answer": "fire", "sound":""},
    {"question": "爪", "answer": "claw", "sound":""},
    {"question": "父", "answer": "father", "sound":""},
    {"question": "爻", "answer": "mix | associate", "sound":""},
    {"question": "爿", "answer": "half of a tree trunk", "sound":""},
    {"question": "片", "answer": "slice | one (of a group)", "sound":""},
    {"question": "牙", "answer": "fang", "sound":""},
    {"question": "牛", "answer": "cow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "犬", "answer": "dog", "sound":""},
    {"question": "玄", "answer": "dark | profound", "sound":""},
    {"question": "玉", "answer": "jade | jewelry", "sound":""},
    {"question": "瓜", "answer": "melon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "瓦", "answer": "tile", "sound":""},
    {"question": "甘", "answer": "sweet", "sound":""},
    {"question": "生", "answer": "life", "sound":""},
    {"question": "用", "answer": "use", "sound":""},
    {"question": "田", "answer": "field", "sound":""},
    {"question": "疋", "answer": "bolt of cloth", "sound":""},
    {"question": "疒", "answer": "sickness", "sound":""},
    {"question": "癶", "answer": "footsteps | legs", "sound":""},
    {"question": "白", "answer": "white", "sound":""},
    {"question": "皮", "answer": "skin | hide", "sound":""},
    {"question": "皿", "answer": "dish", "sound":""},
    {"question": "目", "answer": "eye", "sound":""},
    {"question": "矛", "answer": "spear", "sound":""},
    {"question": "矢", "answer": "arrow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "石", "answer": "stone", "sound":""},
    {"question": "示", "answer": "spirit | ancestor", "sound":""},
    {"question": "禸", "answer": "rump | track", "sound":""},
    {"question": "禾", "answer": "grain", "sound":""},
    {"question": "穴", "answer": "cave", "sound":""},
    {"question": "立", "answer": "stand", "sound":""},
    {"question": "竹", "answer": "bamboo", "sound":""},
    {"question": "米", "answer": "rice", "sound":""},
    {"question": "糸", "answer": "silk", "sound":""},
    {"question": "缶", "answer": "jar", "sound":""},
    {"question": "网", "answer": "net", "sound":""},
    {"question": "羊", "answer": "sheep", "sound":""},
    {"question": "羽", "answer": "feather", "sound":""},
    {"question": "老", "answer": "old", "sound":""},
    {"question": "而", "answer": "and | but", "sound":""},
    {"question": "耒", "answer": "plough", "sound":""},
    {"question": "耳", "answer": "ear", "sound":""},
    {"question": "聿", "answer": "brush", "sound":""},
    {"question": "肉", "answer": "meat", "sound":""},
    {"question": "臣", "answer": "minister", "sound":""},
    {"question": "自", "answer": "self", "sound":""},
    {"question": "至", "answer": "arrive | most", "sound":""},
    {"question": "臼", "answer": "mortar | joint", "sound":""},
    {"question": "舌", "answer": "tongue", "sound":""},
    {"question": "舛", "answer": "oppose", "sound":""},
    {"question": "舟", "answer": "boat", "sound":""},
    {"question": "艮", "answer": "stopping | stillness", "sound":""},
    {"question": "色", "answer": "colour | form", "sound":""},
    {"question": "艸", "answer": "grass", "sound":""},
    {"question": "虍", "answer": "tiger", "sound":""},
    {"question": "虫", "answer": "insect", "sound":""},
    {"question": "血", "answer": "blood", "sound":""},
    {"question": "行", "answer": "go | do", "sound":""},
    {"question": "衣", "answer": "clothes", "sound":""},
    {"question": "襾", "answer": "cover | west", "sound":""},
    {"question": "見", "answer": "see", "sound":""},
    {"question": "角", "answer": "horn", "sound":""},
    {"question": "言" , "answer": "speech", "sound":""},
    {"question": "谷", "answer": "valley", "sound":""},
    {"question": "豆", "answer": "bean", "sound":""},
    {"question": "豕", "answer": "pig", "sound":""},
    {"question": "豸", "answer": "badger", "sound":""},
    {"question": "貝", "answer": "shell", "sound":""},
    {"question": "赤", "answer": "red | bare", "sound":""},
    {"question": "走", "answer": "run", "sound":""},
    {"question": "足", "answer": "foot", "sound":""},
    {"question": "身", "answer": "body", "sound":""},
    {"question": "車", "answer": "cart", "sound":""},
    {"question": "辛", "answer": "bitter", "sound":""},
    {"question": "辰", "answer": "morning", "sound":""},
    {"question": "辵", "answer": "walk", "sound":""},
    {"question": "邑", "answer": "city | community", "sound":""},
    {"question": "酉", "answer": "wine", "sound":""},
    {"question": "釆", "answer": "distinguish", "sound":""},
    {"question": "里", "answer": "village | li", "sound":""},
    {"question": "金", "answer": "gold | metal", "sound":""},
    {"question": "長", "answer": "long | grow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "門", "answer": "gate", "sound":""},
    {"question": "阜", "answer": "mound | dam", "sound":""},
    {"question": "隶", "answer": "slave", "sound":""},
    {"question": "隹", "answer": "small bird", "sound":""},
    {"question": "雨", "answer": "rain", "sound":""},
    {"question": "靑", "answer": "blue", "sound":""},
    {"question": "非", "answer": "wrong", "sound":""},
    {"question": "面", "answer": "face", "sound":""},
    {"question": "革", "answer": "leather", "sound":""},
    {"question": "韋", "answer": "tanned leather", "sound":""},
    {"question": "韭", "answer": "leek", "sound":""},
    {"question": "音", "answer": "sound", "sound":""},
    {"question": "頁", "answer": "page | head", "sound":""},
    {"question": "風", "answer": "wind", "sound":""},
    {"question": "飛", "answer": "flying", "sound":""},
    {"question": "食", "answer": "food", "sound":""},
    {"question": "首", "answer": "head", "sound":""},
    {"question": "香", "answer": "fragrant", "sound":""},
    {"question": "馬", "answer": "horse", "sound":""},
    {"question": "骨", "answer": "bone", "sound":""},
    {"question": "高", "answer": "tall", "sound":""},
    {"question": "髟", "answer": "hair", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鬥", "answer": "fight", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鬯", "answer": "sacrificial wine", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鬲", "answer": "couldron", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鬼", "answer": "demon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "魚", "answer": "fish", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鳥", "answer": "bird", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鹵", "answer": "salt", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鹿", "answer": "deer", "sound":""},
    {"question": "麥", "answer": "wheat", "sound":""},
    {"question": "麻", "answer": "hemp", "sound":""},
    {"question": "黃", "answer": "yellow", "sound":""},
    {"question": "黍", "answer": "millet", "sound":""},
    {"question": "黑", "answer": "black", "sound":""},
    {"question": "黹", "answer": "needlework", "sound":""},
    {"question": "黽", "answer": "frog", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鼎", "answer": "three legged couldron", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鼓", "answer": "drum", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鼠", "answer": "rat", "sound":""},
    {"question": "鼻", "answer": "nose", "sound":""},
    {"question": "齊", "answer": "even | uniformly", "sound":""},
    {"question": "齒", "answer": "teeth", "sound":""},
    {"question": "龍", "answer": "dragon", "sound":""},
    {"question": "龜", "answer": "turtle", "sound":""},
    {"question": "龠", "answer": "flute", "sound":""}
]